[
  {
    "questionText": "to or in another country;overseas;internationally",
    "firstOption": "poll",
    "secondOption": "agitate",
    "thirdOption": "narrow",
    "fourthOption": "abroad",
    "correctOption": "abroad",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "quick , without warning , sudden",
    "firstOption": "assert",
    "secondOption": "acquire",
    "thirdOption": "abrupt",
    "fourthOption": "vibrant",
    "correctOption": "abrupt",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "allowable or satisfactory , permissible",
    "firstOption": "reliably",
    "secondOption": "negligible",
    "thirdOption": "acceptable",
    "fourthOption": "tangible",
    "correctOption": "acceptable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "enthusiastic approval , applause",
    "firstOption": "concur",
    "secondOption": "acclaim",
    "thirdOption": "maintain",
    "fourthOption": "amenity",
    "correctOption": "acclaim",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "being in existence , real or factual , truly",
    "firstOption": "steady",
    "secondOption": "partially",
    "thirdOption": "accurate",
    "fourthOption": "actually",
    "correctOption": "actually",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "displeasing , objectionable , or bad , unfavorable",
    "firstOption": "adverse",
    "secondOption": "analyze",
    "thirdOption": "disperse",
    "fourthOption": "advice",
    "correctOption": "adverse",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "recommendation , suggestion",
    "firstOption": "omit",
    "secondOption": "advice",
    "thirdOption": "diverse",
    "fourthOption": "astute",
    "correctOption": "advice",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "calling attention to , pleasing , creating , appealing",
    "firstOption": "prime",
    "secondOption": "chaotic",
    "thirdOption": "attractive",
    "fourthOption": "narrate",
    "correctOption": "attractive",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "by itself , with no association , independent",
    "firstOption": "allocation",
    "secondOption": "autonomous",
    "thirdOption": "outlandish",
    "fourthOption": "spontaneous",
    "correctOption": "autonomous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "the act of disagreeing;not giving approval;objection",
    "firstOption": "evaporate",
    "secondOption": "disapproval",
    "thirdOption": "disregard",
    "fourthOption": "discreetly",
    "correctOption": "disapproval",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "causing confusion and interruption;disturbing",
    "firstOption": "display",
    "secondOption": "innovative",
    "thirdOption": "selective",
    "fourthOption": "disruptive",
    "correctOption": "disruptive",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having no order or pattern ; by chance,arbitrary,carelessly",
    "firstOption": "particle",
    "secondOption": "supposedly",
    "thirdOption": "haphazardly",
    "fourthOption": "aptly",
    "correctOption": "haphazardly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "having no flaw or mistake , excellent , perfect",
    "firstOption": "widely",
    "secondOption": "persistence",
    "thirdOption": "advanced",
    "fourthOption": "ideal",
    "correctOption": "ideal",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "continuous;refusing to give up;firm in action or decision;constant",
    "firstOption": "feasible",
    "secondOption": "prominent",
    "thirdOption": "heighten",
    "fourthOption": "persistent",
    "correctOption": "persistent",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "extending over a large area , broad",
    "firstOption": "persistent",
    "secondOption": "ideal",
    "thirdOption": "haphazardly",
    "fourthOption": "wide",
    "correctOption": "wide",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ahead of current thought or practice forward thinking , progressive",
    "firstOption": "wide",
    "secondOption": "autonomous",
    "thirdOption": "moderate",
    "fourthOption": "advanced",
    "correctOption": "advanced",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "something that may help one to be successful or to gain something;benefit",
    "firstOption": "handle",
    "secondOption": "ancient",
    "thirdOption": "advantage",
    "fourthOption": "inundate",
    "correctOption": "advantage",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "the coming or appearance of something , arrival",
    "firstOption": "amusement",
    "secondOption": "ancient",
    "thirdOption": "advent",
    "fourthOption": "radiant",
    "correctOption": "advent",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "able to move in a quick and easy way,nimble",
    "firstOption": "arid",
    "secondOption": "valid",
    "thirdOption": "agile",
    "fourthOption": "frail",
    "correctOption": "agile",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "in spite of the fact,regardless of the fact;although",
    "firstOption": "albeit",
    "secondOption": "arid",
    "thirdOption": "forfeit",
    "fourthOption": "ancient",
    "correctOption": "albeit",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to agree to let something happen , not to interface with an action , permit",
    "firstOption": "albeit",
    "secondOption": "agile",
    "thirdOption": "advent",
    "fourthOption": "allow",
    "correctOption": "allow",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "attractive or interesting , alluring",
    "firstOption": "appealing",
    "secondOption": "elicit",
    "thirdOption": "reveal",
    "fourthOption": "vanishing",
    "correctOption": "appealing",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "acclaimed well-known and popular;renowned",
    "firstOption": "selective",
    "secondOption": "unwarranted",
    "thirdOption": "emerge",
    "fourthOption": "celebrated",
    "correctOption": "celebrated",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "modern , up-yo-date , person living at the same time as another person living at the same time as another person",
    "firstOption": "rudimentary",
    "secondOption": "potential",
    "thirdOption": "contemporary",
    "fourthOption": "intensify",
    "correctOption": "contemporary",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to diving among people or to give out;dispense",
    "firstOption": "durable",
    "secondOption": "distribute",
    "thirdOption": "intricate",
    "fourthOption": "intrusive",
    "correctOption": "distribute",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to promote,help,or support;stimulate",
    "firstOption": "encourage",
    "secondOption": "persuade",
    "thirdOption": "curative",
    "fourthOption": "encircle",
    "correctOption": "encourage",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "full of life,action,or power;vigorous",
    "firstOption": "energetic",
    "secondOption": "intrinsic",
    "thirdOption": "emerge",
    "fourthOption": "prophetic",
    "correctOption": "energetic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "weak in health or in body;fragile",
    "firstOption": "flaw",
    "secondOption": "emit",
    "thirdOption": "frail",
    "fourthOption": "toxic",
    "correctOption": "frail",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make pure;to improve;perfect",
    "firstOption": "refine",
    "secondOption": "reject",
    "thirdOption": "emit",
    "fourthOption": "rhythm",
    "correctOption": "refine",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "value in doing something,rewarding",
    "firstOption": "prima",
    "secondOption": "fertile",
    "thirdOption": "extensive",
    "fourthOption": "worthwhile",
    "correctOption": "worthwhile",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to change or make different;modify",
    "firstOption": "alter",
    "secondOption": "parallel",
    "thirdOption": "face",
    "fourthOption": "analyze",
    "correctOption": "alter",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to study something carefully , to separate into parts for study , examine",
    "firstOption": "alter",
    "secondOption": "ancient",
    "thirdOption": "annoying",
    "fourthOption": "analyze",
    "correctOption": "analyze",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "something from a long time ago;very old,old",
    "firstOption": "hasten",
    "secondOption": "refine",
    "thirdOption": "swift",
    "fourthOption": "ancient",
    "correctOption": "ancient",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a slight bother;disturbing to a person;bothersome",
    "firstOption": "annoying",
    "secondOption": "analyze",
    "thirdOption": "solid",
    "fourthOption": "dwelling",
    "correctOption": "annoying",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to think about or prepare for something ahead of time;predict",
    "firstOption": "anticipate",
    "secondOption": "accentuate",
    "thirdOption": "finite",
    "fourthOption": "intrigue",
    "correctOption": "anticipate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to follow established rules or patterns of behavior;adapt",
    "firstOption": "conform",
    "secondOption": "core",
    "thirdOption": "convert",
    "fourthOption": "confirm",
    "correctOption": "conform",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to find out , to observe something, notice",
    "firstOption": "ongoing",
    "secondOption": "intolerable",
    "thirdOption": "enrich",
    "fourthOption": "detect",
    "correctOption": "detect",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make rich , to make something of greater value , enhance",
    "firstOption": "novel",
    "secondOption": "enrich",
    "thirdOption": "convince",
    "fourthOption": "dense",
    "correctOption": "enrich",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make stronger in feeling or quality;heighten",
    "firstOption": "enhance",
    "secondOption": "synthesis",
    "thirdOption": "intensify",
    "fourthOption": "condensed",
    "correctOption": "intensify",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "difficult or painful to experience;not able to accept different ways of thought or behaviour,unbearable",
    "firstOption": "release",
    "secondOption": "fertile",
    "thirdOption": "exaggerate",
    "fourthOption": "intolerable",
    "correctOption": "intolerable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to see and watch carefully , to examine , notice",
    "firstOption": "enrich",
    "secondOption": "intensify",
    "thirdOption": "ongoing",
    "fourthOption": "observe",
    "correctOption": "observe",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "continuing;current",
    "firstOption": "striking",
    "secondOption": "ongoing",
    "thirdOption": "notion",
    "fourthOption": "vanishing",
    "correctOption": "ongoing",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to suggest or plan to do something , suggest",
    "firstOption": "propose",
    "secondOption": "immense",
    "thirdOption": "particle",
    "fourthOption": "ample",
    "correctOption": "propose",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to give back or bring back something;to return to the original condition,revitalize",
    "firstOption": "emerge",
    "secondOption": "distort",
    "thirdOption": "endorse",
    "fourthOption": "restore",
    "correctOption": "restore",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "of great importance;full of life;indispensable",
    "firstOption": "vital",
    "secondOption": "trap",
    "thirdOption": "bear",
    "fourthOption": "ample",
    "correctOption": "vital",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "of unclear meaning;something that can be understood in more than one way;vague",
    "firstOption": "amusement",
    "secondOption": "ambiguous",
    "thirdOption": "motion",
    "fourthOption": "triumph",
    "correctOption": "ambiguous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to be clear in meaning or open to view , easily understood , visible",
    "firstOption": "ambiguous",
    "secondOption": "astute",
    "thirdOption": "arbitrary",
    "fourthOption": "apparent",
    "correctOption": "apparent",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "an action or decision made with little thought order or reason , haphazard",
    "firstOption": "particular",
    "secondOption": "arid",
    "thirdOption": "actually",
    "fourthOption": "arbitrary",
    "correctOption": "arbitrary",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to express or defend oneself strongly ;to state positively , declare",
    "firstOption": "caliber",
    "secondOption": "ancient",
    "thirdOption": "assert",
    "fourthOption": "evident",
    "correctOption": "assert",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "very surprising;astonishing",
    "firstOption": "astounding",
    "secondOption": "actually",
    "thirdOption": "obtain",
    "fourthOption": "dwelling",
    "correctOption": "astounding",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "very intelligent,smart,clever;perceptive",
    "firstOption": "situated",
    "secondOption": "narrate",
    "thirdOption": "astute",
    "fourthOption": "attribute",
    "correctOption": "astute",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to give permission or power to do something , empower",
    "firstOption": "authorize",
    "secondOption": "deceptively",
    "thirdOption": "determined",
    "fourthOption": "astute",
    "correctOption": "authorize",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "making something appear true or good when it is false or bad;misleadingly",
    "firstOption": "deceptively",
    "secondOption": "exceedingly",
    "thirdOption": "recover",
    "fourthOption": "decline",
    "correctOption": "deceptively",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "strong in one s opinion,firm in conviction,to find out;resolute",
    "firstOption": "adverse",
    "secondOption": "determined",
    "thirdOption": "celebrated",
    "fourthOption": "retrieve",
    "correctOption": "determined",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to get the fact , to draw out , to evoke , extract",
    "firstOption": "forbid",
    "secondOption": "elicit",
    "thirdOption": "eliminate",
    "fourthOption": "authentic",
    "correctOption": "elicit",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ban ,to command not do something , to have a dangerous look , bad feeling",
    "firstOption": "forbid",
    "secondOption": "deceptively",
    "thirdOption": "authentic",
    "fourthOption": "elicit",
    "correctOption": "forbid",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make a request,appeal",
    "firstOption": "fertile",
    "secondOption": "practical",
    "thirdOption": "caution",
    "fourthOption": "petition",
    "correctOption": "petition",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to give up control , abdicate",
    "firstOption": "relinquish",
    "secondOption": "zenith",
    "thirdOption": "revive",
    "fourthOption": "delicate",
    "correctOption": "relinquish",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "strong enough to recover from difficulty or disease;tenacious",
    "firstOption": "feign",
    "secondOption": "resilient",
    "thirdOption": "reliable",
    "fourthOption": "petition",
    "correctOption": "resilient",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make it attractive to do something wrong , entice",
    "firstOption": "resilient",
    "secondOption": "petition",
    "thirdOption": "forbid",
    "fourthOption": "tempt",
    "correctOption": "tempt",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to feel with great surprise , astonish",
    "firstOption": "amaze",
    "secondOption": "baffling",
    "thirdOption": "block",
    "fourthOption": "blur",
    "correctOption": "amaze",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to confuse to point at witch no progress can be made , puzzle",
    "firstOption": "prone",
    "secondOption": "idol",
    "thirdOption": "baffle",
    "fourthOption": "ridge",
    "correctOption": "baffle",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to produce,to carry,to show,to endure;yield",
    "firstOption": "defy",
    "secondOption": "span",
    "thirdOption": "halt",
    "fourthOption": "bear",
    "correctOption": "bear",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to prevent movement progress or success , obstruct",
    "firstOption": "block",
    "secondOption": "blur",
    "thirdOption": "amaze",
    "fourthOption": "brilliant",
    "correctOption": "block",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make something difficult to see , cloud",
    "firstOption": "idol",
    "secondOption": "vast",
    "thirdOption": "absurd",
    "fourthOption": "blur",
    "correctOption": "blur",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "intensely , bright or colorful , intelligent",
    "firstOption": "prominent",
    "secondOption": "striking",
    "thirdOption": "brilliant",
    "fourthOption": "evident",
    "correctOption": "brilliant",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to alert someone of danger,warn someone to take care or pay attention to something;warn",
    "firstOption": "motion",
    "secondOption": "confirm",
    "thirdOption": "gain",
    "fourthOption": "caution",
    "correctOption": "caution",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "an invitation to complete , something that demands competitive action or much thought , dare",
    "firstOption": "delicate",
    "secondOption": "challenge",
    "thirdOption": "delighted",
    "fourthOption": "enhance",
    "correctOption": "challenge",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "needing careful treatment;sensitive;easy broken;fragile",
    "firstOption": "finite",
    "secondOption": "dictate",
    "thirdOption": "dominant",
    "fourthOption": "delicate",
    "correctOption": "delicate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to increase in a positive way , such as in value , power , or beauty ",
    "firstOption": "launch",
    "secondOption": "enhance",
    "thirdOption": "exhaust",
    "fourthOption": "engross",
    "correctOption": "enhance",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to interest greatly;fascinate",
    "firstOption": "retrieve",
    "secondOption": "coarse",
    "thirdOption": "intrigue",
    "fourthOption": "interpret",
    "correctOption": "intrigue",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to change a belief or behavior by argument or reason;convince",
    "firstOption": "dense",
    "secondOption": "endure",
    "thirdOption": "span",
    "fourthOption": "persuade",
    "correctOption": "persuade",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to change for another thing to take the place of , substitute",
    "firstOption": "persuade",
    "secondOption": "replace",
    "thirdOption": "shed",
    "fourthOption": "unique",
    "correctOption": "replace",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to throw of naturally , to give out , discard",
    "firstOption": "deep",
    "secondOption": "omit",
    "thirdOption": "shed",
    "fourthOption": "solid",
    "correctOption": "shed",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to be the only one of a kind;special;rare",
    "firstOption": "unravel",
    "secondOption": "unique",
    "thirdOption": "ancient",
    "fourthOption": "erode",
    "correctOption": "unique",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "that most important or most common;mostly",
    "firstOption": "chiefly",
    "secondOption": "compel",
    "thirdOption": "chaotic",
    "fourthOption": "poll",
    "correctOption": "chiefly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not fine or smooth , not delicate , rough",
    "firstOption": "coarse",
    "secondOption": "chiefly",
    "thirdOption": "comparable",
    "fourthOption": "complete",
    "correctOption": "coarse",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ordinary , frequent",
    "firstOption": "commonplace",
    "secondOption": "command",
    "thirdOption": "communicate",
    "fourthOption": "convenient",
    "correctOption": "commonplace",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "being measured or judged by comparison , relatively",
    "firstOption": "comparatively",
    "secondOption": "moderate",
    "thirdOption": "marvel",
    "fourthOption": "partisan",
    "correctOption": "comparatively",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "difficult to understand or explain;having many parts;complicated",
    "firstOption": "novel",
    "secondOption": "conform",
    "thirdOption": "complex",
    "fourthOption": "clever",
    "correctOption": "complex",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "following accepted rules or standards;traditional",
    "firstOption": "conventional",
    "secondOption": "confidential",
    "thirdOption": "critical",
    "fourthOption": "controversial",
    "correctOption": "conventional",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "odd or strange , eager to learn , peculiar",
    "firstOption": "precarious",
    "secondOption": "curious",
    "thirdOption": "unique",
    "fourthOption": "core",
    "correctOption": "curious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "very,to an unusual degree,extremely",
    "firstOption": "display",
    "secondOption": "element",
    "thirdOption": "exceedingly",
    "fourthOption": "exemplify",
    "correctOption": "exceedingly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "no one else;nothing else;not shared;restrictively",
    "firstOption": "decline",
    "secondOption": "acquire",
    "thirdOption": "routinely",
    "fourthOption": "exclusively",
    "correctOption": "exclusively",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "extremely large , massive",
    "firstOption": "core",
    "secondOption": "limber",
    "thirdOption": "immense",
    "fourthOption": "means",
    "correctOption": "immense",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "certainly , really , truly",
    "firstOption": "indeed",
    "secondOption": "rigid",
    "thirdOption": "routinely",
    "fourthOption": "suffer",
    "correctOption": "indeed",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "not easy to bend , firm , inflexible , stiff",
    "firstOption": "poll",
    "secondOption": "frail",
    "thirdOption": "ongoing",
    "fourthOption": "rigid",
    "correctOption": "rigid",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "regularly;usually done;ordinary",
    "firstOption": "nominal",
    "secondOption": "routinely",
    "thirdOption": "reluctantly",
    "fourthOption": "instantly",
    "correctOption": "routinely",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "enough in a satisfying manner , adequately",
    "firstOption": "indeed",
    "secondOption": "immense",
    "thirdOption": "routinely",
    "fourthOption": "sufficiently",
    "correctOption": "sufficiently",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "can be seen , power of imagination or wisdom , especially with regard to the future",
    "firstOption": "sufficiently",
    "secondOption": "indeed",
    "thirdOption": "indicate",
    "fourthOption": "visibly",
    "correctOption": "visibly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "proper , correct or good for the purpose",
    "firstOption": "clarify",
    "secondOption": "visibly",
    "thirdOption": "conceal",
    "fourthOption": "appropriate",
    "correctOption": "appropriate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "explain;to make more easily understood;to make clear",
    "firstOption": "sharply",
    "secondOption": "clarify",
    "thirdOption": "launch",
    "fourthOption": "amenity",
    "correctOption": "clarify",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hide;to prevent from being seen or discovered",
    "firstOption": "nominal",
    "secondOption": "conceal",
    "thirdOption": "compel",
    "fourthOption": "conform",
    "correctOption": "conceal",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "prove , to make certain , give support",
    "firstOption": "rigid",
    "secondOption": "confirm",
    "thirdOption": "notion",
    "fourthOption": "charisma",
    "correctOption": "confirm",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "in an unchanging manner , happening all the time , continually",
    "firstOption": "visibly",
    "secondOption": "approximately",
    "thirdOption": "consume",
    "fourthOption": "constantly",
    "correctOption": "constantly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "practical , easy to reach , near ",
    "firstOption": "convince",
    "secondOption": "prominent",
    "thirdOption": "convenient",
    "fourthOption": "dominant",
    "correctOption": "convenient",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "chief;the central or most important part",
    "firstOption": "lack",
    "secondOption": "ample",
    "thirdOption": "volume",
    "fourthOption": "core",
    "correctOption": "core",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dangerous , very serious or unsafe , finding faults",
    "firstOption": "conceal",
    "secondOption": "critical",
    "thirdOption": "instigate",
    "fourthOption": "mimic",
    "correctOption": "critical",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "deform , to change from the original shape or condition usually in unnatural way ",
    "firstOption": "distort",
    "secondOption": "exports",
    "thirdOption": "rigid",
    "fourthOption": "vast",
    "correctOption": "distort",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "different,various;distinct others",
    "firstOption": "disperse",
    "secondOption": "diverse",
    "thirdOption": "coarse",
    "fourthOption": "severe",
    "correctOption": "diverse",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "thriving , successful , wealthy",
    "firstOption": "enormous",
    "secondOption": "oblivious",
    "thirdOption": "prosperous",
    "fourthOption": "improperly",
    "correctOption": "prosperous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "deliberately,done for a special reason",
    "firstOption": "particular",
    "secondOption": "purposefully",
    "thirdOption": "supposedly",
    "fourthOption": "freshly",
    "correctOption": "purposefully",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disclose , to uncover , to expose",
    "firstOption": "reject",
    "secondOption": "enact",
    "thirdOption": "marvel",
    "fourthOption": "reveal",
    "correctOption": "reveal",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hardly , almost not",
    "firstOption": "stream",
    "secondOption": "scarcely",
    "thirdOption": "entirely",
    "fourthOption": "sharply",
    "correctOption": "scarcely",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hypothetically,according to reasoned,but not proven,point of view",
    "firstOption": "fertile",
    "secondOption": "eventually",
    "thirdOption": "practical",
    "fourthOption": "theoretically",
    "correctOption": "theoretically",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hasten;to go faster",
    "firstOption": "dictate",
    "secondOption": "celebrated",
    "thirdOption": "convert",
    "fourthOption": "accelerate",
    "correctOption": "accelerate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a thin opening caused by breaking , a flaw , fracture",
    "firstOption": "core",
    "secondOption": "accentuate",
    "thirdOption": "accelerate",
    "fourthOption": "crack",
    "correctOption": "crack",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make something new , produce",
    "firstOption": "convince",
    "secondOption": "convenience",
    "thirdOption": "crack",
    "fourthOption": "create",
    "correctOption": "create",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "crawl,to move slowly and quietly close to the ground;to begin happen",
    "firstOption": "freshly",
    "secondOption": "creep",
    "thirdOption": "core",
    "fourthOption": "vast",
    "correctOption": "creep",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "grind , to press together so as to completely distort the shape or nature of the object",
    "firstOption": "myth",
    "secondOption": "crush",
    "thirdOption": "caution",
    "fourthOption": "astute",
    "correctOption": "crush",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "grow , to plan and raise a crop , to encourage growth of a relationship or freindship",
    "firstOption": "culminate",
    "secondOption": "cultivate",
    "thirdOption": "justify",
    "fourthOption": "narrate",
    "correctOption": "cultivate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "impose , to state demands with the poser to enforce",
    "firstOption": "dictate",
    "secondOption": "partially",
    "thirdOption": "distort",
    "fourthOption": "diverse",
    "correctOption": "dictate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "discriminate;to hear,see,or recognize differences",
    "firstOption": "scenic",
    "secondOption": "witticism",
    "thirdOption": "distinguish",
    "fourthOption": "gratifying",
    "correctOption": "distinguish",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "defect,a small sign of damage that makes an item imperfect",
    "firstOption": "flaw",
    "secondOption": "idol",
    "thirdOption": "omit",
    "fourthOption": "dim",
    "correctOption": "flaw",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "gather , the act of collecting a crop , the crops gathered",
    "firstOption": "harvest",
    "secondOption": "harmful",
    "thirdOption": "vague",
    "fourthOption": "advent",
    "correctOption": "harvest",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "reflect , to show , as in mirror",
    "firstOption": "limber",
    "secondOption": "mirror",
    "thirdOption": "drab",
    "fourthOption": "idol",
    "correctOption": "mirror",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "gain , to gain or secure something",
    "firstOption": "bear",
    "secondOption": "motion",
    "thirdOption": "obtain",
    "fourthOption": "archaic",
    "correctOption": "obtain",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fragment,a very small piece of something",
    "firstOption": "handle",
    "secondOption": "fabricate",
    "thirdOption": "particle",
    "fourthOption": "chaotic",
    "correctOption": "particle",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "colonize , to establish a home , to resolve a disagreement",
    "firstOption": "agile",
    "secondOption": "halt",
    "thirdOption": "idol",
    "fourthOption": "settle",
    "correctOption": "settle",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "carry;to move from one place to another",
    "firstOption": "harbor",
    "secondOption": "caliber",
    "thirdOption": "tangible",
    "fourthOption": "transport",
    "correctOption": "transport",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "precise,careful and exact",
    "firstOption": "narrate",
    "secondOption": "moderate",
    "thirdOption": "circulate",
    "fourthOption": "accurate",
    "correctOption": "accurate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "arrange , to place into groups according to type",
    "firstOption": "assert",
    "secondOption": "coarse",
    "thirdOption": "classify",
    "fourthOption": "eclectic",
    "correctOption": "classify",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "money;monetary unit;cash",
    "firstOption": "currency",
    "secondOption": "scenic",
    "thirdOption": "coherent",
    "fourthOption": "convey",
    "correctOption": "currency",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "thorough,far below the surface;complete understanding",
    "firstOption": "dim",
    "secondOption": "deep",
    "thirdOption": "face",
    "fourthOption": "woo",
    "correctOption": "deep",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "thick , closely packed or crowded , difficult to see thorough",
    "firstOption": "dense",
    "secondOption": "core",
    "thirdOption": "renown",
    "fourthOption": "endorse",
    "correctOption": "dense",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to count on , to be supported by , trust",
    "firstOption": "dense",
    "secondOption": "accurate",
    "thirdOption": "classify",
    "fourthOption": "depend on",
    "correctOption": "depend on",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "faint;not bright or clear",
    "firstOption": "idol",
    "secondOption": "drab",
    "thirdOption": "mimic",
    "fourthOption": "dim",
    "correctOption": "dim",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "exhibit , to show , reveal",
    "firstOption": "display",
    "secondOption": "deep",
    "thirdOption": "span",
    "fourthOption": "visibly",
    "correctOption": "display",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "foreign sales , product sold abroad",
    "firstOption": "tedious",
    "secondOption": "exhaust",
    "thirdOption": "evolve",
    "fourthOption": "exports",
    "correctOption": "exports",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "enormous , the state of acting against , not being in agreement",
    "firstOption": "gigantic",
    "secondOption": "eclectic",
    "thirdOption": "chaotic",
    "fourthOption": "erratic",
    "correctOption": "gigantic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "imposing , causing admiration because of an object s importance",
    "firstOption": "impulsively",
    "secondOption": "impressive",
    "thirdOption": "intensify",
    "fourthOption": "course",
    "correctOption": "impressive",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "enduring;forever;without end",
    "firstOption": "obtain",
    "secondOption": "wanton",
    "thirdOption": "lasting",
    "fourthOption": "ongoing",
    "correctOption": "lasting",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "the agency that controls and spends money , a collection of value , bank",
    "firstOption": "exports",
    "secondOption": "impressive",
    "thirdOption": "uniform",
    "fourthOption": "treasury",
    "correctOption": "treasury",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "consistent,every part being the same",
    "firstOption": "uniform",
    "secondOption": "defy",
    "thirdOption": "ridge",
    "fourthOption": "transform",
    "correctOption": "uniform",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "brilliant;lively;powerful;full of action;bright",
    "firstOption": "narrate",
    "secondOption": "gigantic",
    "thirdOption": "vibrant",
    "fourthOption": "vast",
    "correctOption": "vibrant",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "definite;clearly noticed;different",
    "firstOption": "dictate",
    "secondOption": "enact",
    "thirdOption": "mention",
    "fourthOption": "distinct",
    "correctOption": "distinct",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "major , primary or principal , having or exercising control over something",
    "firstOption": "dominant",
    "secondOption": "motion",
    "thirdOption": "maintain",
    "fourthOption": "dime",
    "correctOption": "dominant",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "inactive , not growing or producing , asleep",
    "firstOption": "diligent",
    "secondOption": "dormant",
    "thirdOption": "span",
    "fourthOption": "evident",
    "correctOption": "dormant",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "colorless;lacking color;unintenteresting;boring",
    "firstOption": "drab",
    "secondOption": "myth",
    "thirdOption": "stream",
    "fourthOption": "agile",
    "correctOption": "drab",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "emotional,something that captures the imagination;exciting",
    "firstOption": "dormant",
    "secondOption": "archaic",
    "thirdOption": "dramatic",
    "fourthOption": "chaotic",
    "correctOption": "dramatic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "complex , something with a large number of parts , full of details",
    "firstOption": "elaborate",
    "secondOption": "emerge",
    "thirdOption": "measurable",
    "fourthOption": "evaporate",
    "correctOption": "elaborate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "phenomenal ; unusual in a positive way",
    "firstOption": "selective",
    "secondOption": "scenic",
    "thirdOption": "exceptional",
    "fourthOption": "ancient",
    "correctOption": "exceptional",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dangerous;very risky,unsafe",
    "firstOption": "harvest",
    "secondOption": "hazardous",
    "thirdOption": "account",
    "fourthOption": "tedious",
    "correctOption": "hazardous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "tiny , of little consequence , very small",
    "firstOption": "minuscule",
    "secondOption": "inactive",
    "thirdOption": "circulate",
    "fourthOption": "handle",
    "correctOption": "minuscule",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "prepare,to make ready,first in importance or in time",
    "firstOption": "oblige",
    "secondOption": "prime",
    "thirdOption": "erode",
    "fourthOption": "agile",
    "correctOption": "prime",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "basic , simple , not complex",
    "firstOption": "involuntarily",
    "secondOption": "fundamental",
    "thirdOption": "rudimentary",
    "fourthOption": "maintain",
    "correctOption": "rudimentary",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "easily affected , delicate",
    "firstOption": "sensitive",
    "secondOption": "superficial",
    "thirdOption": "prime",
    "fourthOption": "minuscule",
    "correctOption": "sensitive",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "shallow , simple , not deep , near the surface",
    "firstOption": "superficial",
    "secondOption": "determined",
    "thirdOption": "elicit",
    "fourthOption": "sporadic",
    "correctOption": "superficial",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "filled with fear , frightening ",
    "firstOption": "eliminate",
    "secondOption": "elicit",
    "thirdOption": "superficial",
    "fourthOption": "terrify",
    "correctOption": "terrify",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "strong , powerful , full of action",
    "firstOption": "gigantic",
    "secondOption": "dormant",
    "thirdOption": "perilous",
    "fourthOption": "vigorous",
    "correctOption": "vigorous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "convenience;something that makes life easier or more enjoyable",
    "firstOption": "avert",
    "secondOption": "amenity",
    "thirdOption": "scenic",
    "fourthOption": "emit",
    "correctOption": "amenity",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ruin , to put an end to the existence of sommething",
    "firstOption": "element",
    "secondOption": "dwelling",
    "thirdOption": "disperse",
    "fourthOption": "destroy",
    "correctOption": "destroy",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "circulate , to cause to move in many different directions",
    "firstOption": "release",
    "secondOption": "suspect",
    "thirdOption": "disperse",
    "fourthOption": "distort",
    "correctOption": "disperse",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "house , where people live",
    "firstOption": "refine",
    "secondOption": "dwelling",
    "thirdOption": "striking",
    "fourthOption": "collide",
    "correctOption": "dwelling",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "component;a part of the whole;environment",
    "firstOption": "element",
    "secondOption": "amusement",
    "thirdOption": "evident",
    "fourthOption": "evoke",
    "correctOption": "element",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "primary;simple in structurre,easy to do",
    "firstOption": "eliminate",
    "secondOption": "culminate",
    "thirdOption": "elementary",
    "fourthOption": "amenity",
    "correctOption": "elementary",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "delete;to remove;free oneself of something",
    "firstOption": "eliminate",
    "secondOption": "albeit",
    "thirdOption": "evident",
    "fourthOption": "emerge",
    "correctOption": "eliminate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "highlight , to show that something is especially important or exceptional",
    "firstOption": "release",
    "secondOption": "prime",
    "thirdOption": "emphasize",
    "fourthOption": "emit",
    "correctOption": "emphasize",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "surround;to make a circle around",
    "firstOption": "encircle",
    "secondOption": "circulate",
    "thirdOption": "reliable",
    "fourthOption": "measurable",
    "correctOption": "encircle",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "inconsistent , no regular pattern in thinking or movement , changeable without reason",
    "firstOption": "erratic",
    "secondOption": "trait",
    "thirdOption": "enact",
    "fourthOption": "unravel",
    "correctOption": "erratic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "overstate,to make something more than what it is ",
    "firstOption": "inordinate",
    "secondOption": "anticipate",
    "thirdOption": "assert",
    "fourthOption": "exaggerate",
    "correctOption": "exaggerate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "remark;to say;relate in written from",
    "firstOption": "mention",
    "secondOption": "reaction",
    "thirdOption": "renown",
    "fourthOption": "entirely",
    "correctOption": "mention",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dock , a place where boats arrive to take on or unload cargo and passengers",
    "firstOption": "encircle",
    "secondOption": "prime",
    "thirdOption": "mention",
    "fourthOption": "pier",
    "correctOption": "pier",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "commonplace,existing widely or commonly",
    "firstOption": "prevalent",
    "secondOption": "marvel",
    "thirdOption": "prominent",
    "fourthOption": "dramatic",
    "correctOption": "prevalent",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "free;to allow to come out;to give freedom",
    "firstOption": "release",
    "secondOption": "restore",
    "thirdOption": "selective",
    "fourthOption": "requisite",
    "correctOption": "release",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "assist;to be useful or helpful",
    "firstOption": "benefit",
    "secondOption": "avert",
    "thirdOption": "advent",
    "fourthOption": "assert",
    "correctOption": "benefit",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unaware;unable to see or understand;to conceal;showing poor judgment or understanding",
    "firstOption": "varied",
    "secondOption": "blind",
    "thirdOption": "arid",
    "fourthOption": "elude",
    "correctOption": "blind",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make larger or greater",
    "firstOption": "persuade",
    "secondOption": "broaden",
    "thirdOption": "span",
    "fourthOption": "odd",
    "correctOption": "broaden",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "thrive;growing at a fast pace",
    "firstOption": "curious",
    "secondOption": "oblige",
    "thirdOption": "avert",
    "fourthOption": "burgeon",
    "correctOption": "burgeon",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "noticeable;attractive attention",
    "firstOption": "purposefully",
    "secondOption": "tedious",
    "thirdOption": "conspicuously",
    "fourthOption": "discreetly",
    "correctOption": "conspicuously",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to ask for something in a strong way , insist",
    "firstOption": "demand",
    "secondOption": "conspicuously",
    "thirdOption": "enormous",
    "fourthOption": "endorse",
    "correctOption": "demand",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "support;to express approval",
    "firstOption": "unique",
    "secondOption": "engross",
    "thirdOption": "renown",
    "fourthOption": "endorse",
    "correctOption": "endorse",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "tremendous , very large",
    "firstOption": "erode",
    "secondOption": "enormous",
    "thirdOption": "crush",
    "fourthOption": "mirror",
    "correctOption": "enormous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "thoroughly , completely",
    "firstOption": "vital",
    "secondOption": "idol",
    "thirdOption": "prime",
    "fourthOption": "entirely",
    "correctOption": "entirely",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "deteriorate;to wear;disappear slowly",
    "firstOption": "evolve",
    "secondOption": "erode",
    "thirdOption": "ride",
    "fourthOption": "evoke",
    "correctOption": "erode",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disappear;to vanish",
    "firstOption": "elaborate",
    "secondOption": "evaporate",
    "thirdOption": "instigate",
    "fourthOption": "amenity",
    "correctOption": "evaporate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "retrieve ,to get back , to have something returned",
    "firstOption": "concur",
    "secondOption": "peculiar",
    "thirdOption": "recover",
    "fourthOption": "chaotic",
    "correctOption": "recover",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "rumored;to know by report;unconfirmed;supposedly",
    "firstOption": "reportedly",
    "secondOption": "scarcely",
    "thirdOption": "overtly",
    "fourthOption": "sporadic",
    "correctOption": "reportedly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "switch;a change in position or direction",
    "firstOption": "evoke",
    "secondOption": "shift",
    "thirdOption": "scenic",
    "fourthOption": "briefly",
    "correctOption": "shift",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "endure , to experience difficulty , to to worsen in quality , to experience pain",
    "firstOption": "recover",
    "secondOption": "reportedly",
    "thirdOption": "shift",
    "fourthOption": "suffer",
    "correctOption": "suffer",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "celebrity , a very important or famous person usually associated with a high position in goverenment",
    "firstOption": "security",
    "secondOption": "routinely",
    "thirdOption": "dignitary",
    "fourthOption": "instigate",
    "correctOption": "dignitary",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "critical , of great importance , extremely necessary",
    "firstOption": "curative",
    "secondOption": "vital",
    "thirdOption": "crucial",
    "fourthOption": "compel",
    "correctOption": "crucial",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "evade",
    "firstOption": "elude",
    "secondOption": "evoke",
    "thirdOption": "hue",
    "fourthOption": "erode",
    "correctOption": "elude",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "apparent,easy to see,usually because of some proof",
    "firstOption": "evoke",
    "secondOption": "elude",
    "thirdOption": "advent",
    "fourthOption": "evident",
    "correctOption": "evident",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "deplete;to use completely;to expend all energy;very thorough",
    "firstOption": "emit",
    "secondOption": "exhaust",
    "thirdOption": "account",
    "fourthOption": "hasten",
    "correctOption": "exhaust",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "comprehensive , large in area or number , to offer , to make longer ",
    "firstOption": "selective",
    "secondOption": "dense",
    "thirdOption": "extensive",
    "fourthOption": "exhaust",
    "correctOption": "extensive",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "highly , very , to the vary end , the highest extent",
    "firstOption": "extremely",
    "secondOption": "hero",
    "thirdOption": "facet",
    "fourthOption": "obliviously",
    "correctOption": "extremely",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "confront;to be in the presence of and oppose",
    "firstOption": "handle",
    "secondOption": "face",
    "thirdOption": "shed",
    "fourthOption": "myth",
    "correctOption": "face",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "aspect;element or component",
    "firstOption": "creep",
    "secondOption": "facet",
    "thirdOption": "valid",
    "fourthOption": "avert",
    "correctOption": "facet",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a person remembered for an act of goodness or bravery , idol",
    "firstOption": "facet",
    "secondOption": "face",
    "thirdOption": "hero",
    "fourthOption": "shed",
    "correctOption": "hero",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "remote,something that cannot be reached or communicated with",
    "firstOption": "acceptable",
    "secondOption": "classify",
    "thirdOption": "inaccessible",
    "fourthOption": "extensive",
    "correctOption": "inaccessible",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "evidently , in a clear , easy to understand way",
    "firstOption": "robust",
    "secondOption": "briefly",
    "thirdOption": "visibly",
    "fourthOption": "obviously",
    "correctOption": "obviously",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "expectedly;in a way that foretells future events",
    "firstOption": "undeniable",
    "secondOption": "readily",
    "thirdOption": "presumable",
    "fourthOption": "predictably",
    "correctOption": "predictably",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to find an answer , resolve",
    "firstOption": "solve",
    "secondOption": "predict",
    "thirdOption": "suitable",
    "fourthOption": "briefly",
    "correctOption": "solve",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "appropriate;correct;convenient",
    "firstOption": "initiate",
    "secondOption": "suitable",
    "thirdOption": "measurable",
    "fourthOption": "formidable",
    "correctOption": "suitable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "more than enough , sufficient",
    "firstOption": "ample",
    "secondOption": "arid",
    "thirdOption": "avoid",
    "fourthOption": "event",
    "correctOption": "ample",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dry;being of little rain or water",
    "firstOption": "varied",
    "secondOption": "arid",
    "thirdOption": "pass",
    "fourthOption": "gain",
    "correctOption": "arid",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to miss or keep away from , avert",
    "firstOption": "arid",
    "secondOption": "avoid",
    "thirdOption": "ample",
    "fourthOption": "feign",
    "correctOption": "avoid",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "resist , to show little fear or regard for rules or established norms , to challenge",
    "firstOption": "chiefly",
    "secondOption": "vast",
    "thirdOption": "defy",
    "fourthOption": "myth",
    "correctOption": "defy",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "legislate;to pass a low",
    "firstOption": "enact",
    "secondOption": "halt",
    "thirdOption": "scenic",
    "fourthOption": "elicit",
    "correctOption": "enact",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "regular , smooth , in equal parts , equitable",
    "firstOption": "even",
    "secondOption": "feign",
    "thirdOption": "avert",
    "fourthOption": "arid",
    "correctOption": "even",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "simulate , to pretend ,make believe",
    "firstOption": "fertile",
    "secondOption": "gain",
    "thirdOption": "feign",
    "fourthOption": "mention",
    "correctOption": "feign",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "rich;able to produce abundantly",
    "firstOption": "fertile",
    "secondOption": "feign",
    "thirdOption": "readily",
    "fourthOption": "perceive",
    "correctOption": "fertile",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "recently,caught or produced not long ago",
    "firstOption": "freshly",
    "secondOption": "normally",
    "thirdOption": "amenity",
    "fourthOption": "reject",
    "correctOption": "freshly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "role , the normal purpose of something",
    "firstOption": "function",
    "secondOption": "placid",
    "thirdOption": "hasten",
    "fourthOption": "finite",
    "correctOption": "function",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "essential;a primary or basic element",
    "firstOption": "advent",
    "secondOption": "fundamental",
    "thirdOption": "unravel",
    "fourthOption": "turbulent",
    "correctOption": "fundamental",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "arbitrary,not chosen carefully;unplanned",
    "firstOption": "culminate",
    "secondOption": "indiscriminate",
    "thirdOption": "intricate",
    "fourthOption": "instigate",
    "correctOption": "indiscriminate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "discriminating;carefully chosen",
    "firstOption": "requisite",
    "secondOption": "plentiful",
    "thirdOption": "curative",
    "fourthOption": "selective",
    "correctOption": "selective",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "expensive;having a lot of room",
    "firstOption": "account",
    "secondOption": "perilous",
    "thirdOption": "spacious",
    "fourthOption": "reaction",
    "correctOption": "spacious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "survive;to fight without surrender;to persist",
    "firstOption": "instantly",
    "secondOption": "intricate",
    "thirdOption": "striking",
    "fourthOption": "withstand",
    "correctOption": "withstand",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "sturdy , something that last a long time",
    "firstOption": "enhance",
    "secondOption": "durable",
    "thirdOption": "erratic",
    "fourthOption": "tangible",
    "correctOption": "durable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to prefer , advantageous , support",
    "firstOption": "gain",
    "secondOption": "halt",
    "thirdOption": "durable",
    "fourthOption": "favor",
    "correctOption": "favor",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to obtain something needed or useful, to gainful increase the amount of something , attain",
    "firstOption": "gain",
    "secondOption": "favor",
    "thirdOption": "durable",
    "fourthOption": "tangible",
    "correctOption": "gain",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to produce , create",
    "firstOption": "generate",
    "secondOption": "halt",
    "thirdOption": "favor",
    "fourthOption": "cease",
    "correctOption": "generate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "stop , to stop or discontinue",
    "firstOption": "halt",
    "secondOption": "omit",
    "thirdOption": "shift",
    "fourthOption": "vast",
    "correctOption": "halt",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "manage;to deal with or control",
    "firstOption": "shed",
    "secondOption": "aptly",
    "thirdOption": "handle",
    "fourthOption": "face",
    "correctOption": "handle",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "shelter,to give protection;to not express a desire or opinion,usually bad",
    "firstOption": "harbor",
    "secondOption": "hasten",
    "thirdOption": "coarse",
    "fourthOption": "varied",
    "correctOption": "harbor",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unhealthy , something that cause pain or damage",
    "firstOption": "halt",
    "secondOption": "harmful",
    "thirdOption": "baffle",
    "fourthOption": "reject",
    "correctOption": "harmful",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "meaningless,not important;of little value",
    "firstOption": "enlighten",
    "secondOption": "insignificant",
    "thirdOption": "brilliant",
    "fourthOption": "maintain",
    "correctOption": "insignificant",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "baffling,not easily understood or figured out",
    "firstOption": "mirror",
    "secondOption": "mysterious",
    "thirdOption": "pattern",
    "fourthOption": "ambiguous",
    "correctOption": "mysterious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dangerous",
    "firstOption": "periodic",
    "secondOption": "ambiguous",
    "thirdOption": "overlook",
    "fourthOption": "perilous",
    "correctOption": "perilous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "reschedule at a later time , put off , delay",
    "firstOption": "perilous",
    "secondOption": "harmful",
    "thirdOption": "promote",
    "fourthOption": "postpone",
    "correctOption": "postpone",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "boost , to encourage or advertise , to elevate in rank or grade",
    "firstOption": "recover",
    "secondOption": "promote",
    "thirdOption": "agitate",
    "fourthOption": "narrate",
    "correctOption": "promote",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "refuse;to refuse",
    "firstOption": "reject",
    "secondOption": "robust",
    "thirdOption": "albeit",
    "fourthOption": "prevalent",
    "correctOption": "reject",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "significant,important;strongly made;of value",
    "firstOption": "spontaneous",
    "secondOption": "obtain",
    "thirdOption": "substantial",
    "fourthOption": "impartial",
    "correctOption": "substantial",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "meticulous , showing serious purpose , one who works carefully and with enthusiasm",
    "firstOption": "conscientious",
    "secondOption": "conceivably",
    "thirdOption": "mention",
    "fourthOption": "conceal",
    "correctOption": "conscientious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "communicate;to make something know to others;to communicate",
    "firstOption": "convey",
    "secondOption": "dense",
    "thirdOption": "concur",
    "fourthOption": "robust",
    "correctOption": "convey",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "include , to surround completely , to envelop",
    "firstOption": "enormous",
    "secondOption": "encompass",
    "thirdOption": "compel",
    "fourthOption": "engross",
    "correctOption": "encompass",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "growth;the act of making larger",
    "firstOption": "notion",
    "secondOption": "transform",
    "thirdOption": "reflection",
    "fourthOption": "expansion",
    "correctOption": "expansion",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "intensify;to cause to become greater",
    "firstOption": "reject",
    "secondOption": "heighten",
    "thirdOption": "agitate",
    "fourthOption": "wanton",
    "correctOption": "heighten",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "emphasize,to emphasize the part of a greater whole",
    "firstOption": "brilliant",
    "secondOption": "highlight",
    "thirdOption": "shift",
    "fourthOption": "tightly",
    "correctOption": "highlight",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "by accident , without paying attention , unexpectedly , carelessly",
    "firstOption": "inadvertently",
    "secondOption": "highlight",
    "thirdOption": "infancy",
    "fourthOption": "retrieve",
    "correctOption": "inadvertently",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unavoidable;something that cannot be prevented from happening",
    "firstOption": "tangible",
    "secondOption": "inevitable",
    "thirdOption": "feasible",
    "fourthOption": "delicate",
    "correctOption": "inevitable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "beginning , in the stages of development",
    "firstOption": "isolate",
    "secondOption": "lack",
    "thirdOption": "infancy",
    "fourthOption": "span",
    "correctOption": "infancy",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "causes by something that can not be explained by the laws of nature , astonishingly",
    "firstOption": "inevitable",
    "secondOption": "span",
    "thirdOption": "isolate",
    "fourthOption": "miraculously",
    "correctOption": "miraculously",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "recover;to find and bring back",
    "firstOption": "element",
    "secondOption": "retrieve",
    "thirdOption": "reject",
    "fourthOption": "enrich",
    "correctOption": "retrieve",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "methodically;done according to a plan",
    "firstOption": "exceedingly",
    "secondOption": "consistently",
    "thirdOption": "contemporary",
    "fourthOption": "systematically",
    "correctOption": "systematically",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "doubtful , not probable",
    "firstOption": "unlikely",
    "secondOption": "volume",
    "thirdOption": "undeniably",
    "fourthOption": "reliably",
    "correctOption": "unlikely",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unjustified,without good reason or cause;inappropriate",
    "firstOption": "unwarranted",
    "secondOption": "dormant",
    "thirdOption": "encourage",
    "fourthOption": "trait",
    "correctOption": "unwarranted",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "apex;the highest point",
    "firstOption": "defy",
    "secondOption": "zenith",
    "thirdOption": "endure",
    "fourthOption": "dense",
    "correctOption": "zenith",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disturb;to shake or move;to cause worry",
    "firstOption": "arid",
    "secondOption": "maintain",
    "thirdOption": "agitate",
    "fourthOption": "ridge",
    "correctOption": "agitate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "secret;to be said or written in recret",
    "firstOption": "sufficient",
    "secondOption": "evident",
    "thirdOption": "offensive",
    "fourthOption": "confidential",
    "correctOption": "confidential",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "elated,to be satisfied;very happy",
    "firstOption": "delighted",
    "secondOption": "well-suited",
    "thirdOption": "limber",
    "fourthOption": "antiquated",
    "correctOption": "delighted",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cautiously , in a careful , polite manner",
    "firstOption": "discreetly",
    "secondOption": "instantly",
    "thirdOption": "overtly",
    "fourthOption": "distinct",
    "correctOption": "discreetly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "proven , proven with written evidence",
    "firstOption": "immense",
    "secondOption": "documented",
    "thirdOption": "decline",
    "fourthOption": "unwarranted",
    "correctOption": "documented",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "steadily;slowly,but surely",
    "firstOption": "actually",
    "secondOption": "gradually",
    "thirdOption": "eventually",
    "fourthOption": "readily",
    "correctOption": "gradually",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to have an effect on a person s point of view or behavior , to change the course of events , affect",
    "firstOption": "discreetly",
    "secondOption": "documented",
    "thirdOption": "influence",
    "fourthOption": "inordinate",
    "correctOption": "influence",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "excessive,a large amount or quantity;more than reasonable",
    "firstOption": "delicate",
    "secondOption": "anticipate",
    "thirdOption": "enormous",
    "fourthOption": "inordinate",
    "correctOption": "inordinate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "immediately , happening immediately , in a short period of time",
    "firstOption": "routinely",
    "secondOption": "visibly",
    "thirdOption": "justify",
    "fourthOption": "instantly",
    "correctOption": "instantly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "deliberately;with define purpose and planning",
    "firstOption": "intentionally",
    "secondOption": "eventually",
    "thirdOption": "intolerable",
    "fourthOption": "instantly",
    "correctOption": "intentionally",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "inherent , being a primary part of something",
    "firstOption": "enrich",
    "secondOption": "intrinsic",
    "thirdOption": "elicit",
    "fourthOption": "entirely",
    "correctOption": "intrinsic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "overwhelm , to flood",
    "firstOption": "endure",
    "secondOption": "isolated",
    "thirdOption": "persuade",
    "fourthOption": "inundate",
    "correctOption": "inundate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to become concerned with or connected to  , include",
    "firstOption": "inundate",
    "secondOption": "involve",
    "thirdOption": "nominal",
    "fourthOption": "intrinsic",
    "correctOption": "involve",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "moderate , very small , in form , but not in substance",
    "firstOption": "nominal",
    "secondOption": "refine",
    "thirdOption": "potent",
    "fourthOption": "conceal",
    "correctOption": "nominal",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "supposedly , reported but not confirmed",
    "firstOption": "inevitable",
    "secondOption": "presumably",
    "thirdOption": "remarkable",
    "fourthOption": "predictably",
    "correctOption": "presumably",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ridiculous , clearly false , without reason",
    "firstOption": "abrupt",
    "secondOption": "found",
    "thirdOption": "assert",
    "fourthOption": "absurd",
    "correctOption": "absurd",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "the act of using or treating things in an incorrect way",
    "firstOption": "absurd",
    "secondOption": "abuse",
    "thirdOption": "found",
    "fourthOption": "abrupt",
    "correctOption": "abuse",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "distribution , a share , a part set aside for a special purpose , an assignment of portion",
    "firstOption": "allocation",
    "secondOption": "archaic",
    "thirdOption": "preconception",
    "fourthOption": "acquire",
    "correctOption": "allocation",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "equalized;a state where everything is of the same size or weight",
    "firstOption": "balanced",
    "secondOption": "arid",
    "thirdOption": "parallel",
    "fourthOption": "placid",
    "correctOption": "balanced",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "the act of using carefully , setting aside for future use , preservation",
    "firstOption": "balanced",
    "secondOption": "abuse",
    "thirdOption": "conservation",
    "fourthOption": "allocation",
    "correctOption": "conservation",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "incorrect , having errors",
    "firstOption": "precious",
    "secondOption": "caution",
    "thirdOption": "fallacious",
    "fourthOption": "curious",
    "correctOption": "fallacious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "possible;able to be done",
    "firstOption": "remarkable",
    "secondOption": "measurable",
    "thirdOption": "freshly",
    "fourthOption": "feasible",
    "correctOption": "feasible",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "shortage;a need for;an insufficient amount",
    "firstOption": "lack",
    "secondOption": "vast",
    "thirdOption": "span",
    "fourthOption": "omit",
    "correctOption": "lack",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "flexible;to be stretched,easily shaped",
    "firstOption": "limber",
    "secondOption": "alter",
    "thirdOption": "dim",
    "fourthOption": "prime",
    "correctOption": "limber",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "methods , ways",
    "firstOption": "enact",
    "secondOption": "face",
    "thirdOption": "defy",
    "fourthOption": "means",
    "correctOption": "means",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "thin , small from one side to the other , limited",
    "firstOption": "enormous",
    "secondOption": "harbor",
    "thirdOption": "narrow",
    "fourthOption": "narrate",
    "correctOption": "narrow",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bias;an opinion formed in advance without experience or knowledge of something",
    "firstOption": "petition",
    "secondOption": "proportions",
    "thirdOption": "conscientious",
    "fourthOption": "preconception",
    "correctOption": "preconception",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "energetic , showing good health , in good shape in",
    "firstOption": "crush",
    "secondOption": "vast",
    "thirdOption": "robust",
    "fourthOption": "exhaust",
    "correctOption": "robust",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "constant;firm,reliable,dependable",
    "firstOption": "trait",
    "secondOption": "pass",
    "thirdOption": "foster",
    "fourthOption": "steady",
    "correctOption": "steady",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "fast;quick",
    "firstOption": "weak",
    "secondOption": "assert",
    "thirdOption": "steady",
    "fourthOption": "swift",
    "correctOption": "swift",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "old-fashioned,too old to be presently useful,outmoded",
    "firstOption": "unique",
    "secondOption": "antiquated",
    "thirdOption": "accentuate",
    "fourthOption": "assimilate",
    "correctOption": "antiquated",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "logical;well reasoned;ideas that are clearly presented",
    "firstOption": "potent",
    "secondOption": "moderate",
    "thirdOption": "coherent",
    "fourthOption": "currency",
    "correctOption": "coherent",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to grow , to increase , to become more , complete",
    "firstOption": "develop",
    "secondOption": "fabricate",
    "thirdOption": "coherent",
    "fourthOption": "antiquated",
    "correctOption": "develop",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "invent,to make up;usually with an intend to fool or trick",
    "firstOption": "ridge",
    "secondOption": "accurate",
    "thirdOption": "inundate",
    "fourthOption": "fabricate",
    "correctOption": "fabricate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "probe , a careful examination in order to determine facts",
    "firstOption": "initiate",
    "secondOption": "allocation",
    "thirdOption": "investigation",
    "fourthOption": "install",
    "correctOption": "investigation",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to sense , to be aware , observe",
    "firstOption": "notice",
    "secondOption": "notion",
    "thirdOption": "novel",
    "fourthOption": "normally",
    "correctOption": "notice",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "typically , commonly , usually",
    "firstOption": "poll",
    "secondOption": "normally",
    "thirdOption": "dormant",
    "fourthOption": "actually",
    "correctOption": "normally",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "concept;an idea,belief,or opinion",
    "firstOption": "function",
    "secondOption": "omit",
    "thirdOption": "caution",
    "fourthOption": "notion",
    "correctOption": "notion",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "original;something unusual,uncommon;new",
    "firstOption": "nominal",
    "secondOption": "novel",
    "thirdOption": "alter",
    "fourthOption": "erode",
    "correctOption": "novel",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "resistance, the state of acting against , not being in agreement",
    "firstOption": "opposition",
    "secondOption": "reaction",
    "thirdOption": "mention",
    "fourthOption": "caution",
    "correctOption": "opposition",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to make a written or oral notation , to copy , register",
    "firstOption": "notice",
    "secondOption": "notion",
    "thirdOption": "record",
    "fourthOption": "relate",
    "correctOption": "record",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "communicate;to tell,to show a connection between two things",
    "firstOption": "restore",
    "secondOption": "moderate",
    "thirdOption": "relate",
    "fourthOption": "frail",
    "correctOption": "relate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "speculate;to think that sth is true,but having no proof",
    "firstOption": "obstruct",
    "secondOption": "suspect",
    "thirdOption": "superior",
    "fourthOption": "justify",
    "correctOption": "suspect",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "objective;with no preconceptions",
    "firstOption": "isolated",
    "secondOption": "bear",
    "thirdOption": "placid",
    "fourthOption": "unbiased",
    "correctOption": "unbiased",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "diverse , being of many different types",
    "firstOption": "refine",
    "secondOption": "deep",
    "thirdOption": "vast",
    "fourthOption": "varied",
    "correctOption": "varied",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "emphasize,to highlight,to give more importance to",
    "firstOption": "accelerate",
    "secondOption": "accentuate",
    "thirdOption": "offensive",
    "fourthOption": "persuade",
    "correctOption": "accentuate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "conceal , to hide the usual appearance of something",
    "firstOption": "distribute",
    "secondOption": "disguise",
    "thirdOption": "endure",
    "fourthOption": "distinct",
    "correctOption": "disguise",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to provide money , fund",
    "firstOption": "finance",
    "secondOption": "initiate",
    "thirdOption": "accentuate",
    "fourthOption": "disguise",
    "correctOption": "finance",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "launch , to begin , to establish ",
    "firstOption": "initiate",
    "secondOption": "cultivate",
    "thirdOption": "intricate",
    "fourthOption": "relate",
    "correctOption": "initiate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "something newly introduced , creative",
    "firstOption": "initiate",
    "secondOption": "finance",
    "thirdOption": "disguise",
    "fourthOption": "innovative",
    "correctOption": "innovative",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "relate;to tell a story",
    "firstOption": "initiate",
    "secondOption": "astute",
    "thirdOption": "narrate",
    "fourthOption": "moderate",
    "correctOption": "narrate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "nonetheless,in spite of that",
    "firstOption": "reportedly",
    "secondOption": "nevertheless",
    "thirdOption": "adverse",
    "fourthOption": "fertile",
    "correctOption": "nevertheless",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "now and then , once in a while",
    "firstOption": "omit",
    "secondOption": "narrate",
    "thirdOption": "fertile",
    "fourthOption": "occasionally",
    "correctOption": "occasionally",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "neglect , to leave out",
    "firstOption": "poll",
    "secondOption": "prompt",
    "thirdOption": "temp",
    "fourthOption": "omit",
    "correctOption": "omit",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bizarre;strange and unpleasant;beyond accepted norms",
    "firstOption": "attractive",
    "secondOption": "outlandish",
    "thirdOption": "lack",
    "fourthOption": "justify",
    "correctOption": "outlandish",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "conquer,to defeat,fight with success;to take control of an individual",
    "firstOption": "promote",
    "secondOption": "recover",
    "thirdOption": "refine",
    "fourthOption": "overcome",
    "correctOption": "overcome",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "somewhat",
    "firstOption": "unlikely",
    "secondOption": "harmful",
    "thirdOption": "partially",
    "fourthOption": "practical",
    "correctOption": "partially",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "approve,to accept formally by vote n a",
    "firstOption": "pass",
    "secondOption": "dim",
    "thirdOption": "gain",
    "fourthOption": "trap",
    "correctOption": "pass",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "depict;to represent;to act",
    "firstOption": "display",
    "secondOption": "portray",
    "thirdOption": "normally",
    "fourthOption": "narrow",
    "correctOption": "portray",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to represent , to act , depict",
    "firstOption": "normally",
    "secondOption": "submit",
    "thirdOption": "valid",
    "fourthOption": "caliber",
    "correctOption": "submit",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "decrease;to move from good to bad,or from much little to little,to refuse;",
    "firstOption": "emerge",
    "secondOption": "decline",
    "thirdOption": "volume",
    "fourthOption": "gain",
    "correctOption": "decline",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "collect",
    "firstOption": "gather",
    "secondOption": "clever",
    "thirdOption": "marvel",
    "fourthOption": "avert",
    "correctOption": "gather",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "movement,the state of changing one s position",
    "firstOption": "motion",
    "secondOption": "mention",
    "thirdOption": "valid",
    "fourthOption": "alter",
    "correctOption": "motion",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "biased,strongly supporting a group or point of view",
    "firstOption": "lasting",
    "secondOption": "pass",
    "thirdOption": "partisan",
    "fourthOption": "arid",
    "correctOption": "partisan",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "habit;a regular,repeated arrangement or action",
    "firstOption": "face",
    "secondOption": "wanton",
    "thirdOption": "caution",
    "fourthOption": "pattern",
    "correctOption": "pattern",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "events;natural events or facts;strange or notable",
    "firstOption": "novel",
    "secondOption": "phenomena",
    "thirdOption": "propose",
    "fourthOption": "nominal",
    "correctOption": "phenomena",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "humanitarian;a feeling of love for people,usually resulting in financial aid to worthy cause",
    "firstOption": "periodic",
    "secondOption": "proportions",
    "thirdOption": "philanthropic",
    "fourthOption": "placid",
    "correctOption": "philanthropic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "calm;quiet,not easy upset",
    "firstOption": "valid",
    "secondOption": "gain",
    "thirdOption": "balanced",
    "fourthOption": "placid",
    "correctOption": "placid",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "abundant;more than sufficient",
    "firstOption": "harmful",
    "secondOption": "benefit",
    "thirdOption": "encircle",
    "fourthOption": "plentiful",
    "correctOption": "plentiful",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "response,a reply;a change that occurs when substances are mixed",
    "firstOption": "reaction",
    "secondOption": "perceive",
    "thirdOption": "eclectic",
    "fourthOption": "tedious",
    "correctOption": "reaction",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "pulse;a regular pattern,usually in music",
    "firstOption": "prompt",
    "secondOption": "rhythm",
    "thirdOption": "trait",
    "fourthOption": "vital",
    "correctOption": "rhythm",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "picturesque , concerning pleasant natural surrounding",
    "firstOption": "deep",
    "secondOption": "steady",
    "thirdOption": "zenith",
    "fourthOption": "scenic",
    "correctOption": "scenic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "superficial;not far from top to bottom",
    "firstOption": "spacious",
    "secondOption": "shallow",
    "thirdOption": "settle",
    "fourthOption": "frail",
    "correctOption": "shallow",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "protected , a protected from harmful elements , isolated from reality",
    "firstOption": "scattered",
    "secondOption": "settle",
    "thirdOption": "relate",
    "fourthOption": "sheltered",
    "correctOption": "sheltered",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disappearing;going out of sight",
    "firstOption": "vanishing",
    "secondOption": "shift",
    "thirdOption": "dwelling",
    "fourthOption": "annoying",
    "correctOption": "vanishing",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "story , a report of an event , money kept in bank , a statement of something used or received , usually a financial",
    "firstOption": "ancient",
    "secondOption": "robust",
    "thirdOption": "wanton",
    "fourthOption": "account",
    "correctOption": "account",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ancient,very old,old-fashioned,no longer used",
    "firstOption": "dramatic",
    "secondOption": "relate",
    "thirdOption": "archaic",
    "fourthOption": "obtain",
    "correctOption": "archaic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "accelerate , to cause to go faster , move forward more quickly",
    "firstOption": "face",
    "secondOption": "alter",
    "thirdOption": "hasten",
    "fourthOption": "facet",
    "correctOption": "hasten",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "color",
    "firstOption": "avert",
    "secondOption": "odd",
    "thirdOption": "omit",
    "fourthOption": "hue",
    "correctOption": "hue",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "a visual image , typically used to explain , picture",
    "firstOption": "hasten",
    "secondOption": "archaic",
    "thirdOption": "inactive",
    "fourthOption": "illustration",
    "correctOption": "illustration",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "idle;not moving;not involved",
    "firstOption": "inactive",
    "secondOption": "notion",
    "thirdOption": "practical",
    "fourthOption": "placid",
    "correctOption": "inactive",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "complex;having many parts;finely detailed",
    "firstOption": "cultivate",
    "secondOption": "intrigue",
    "thirdOption": "distribute",
    "fourthOption": "intricate",
    "correctOption": "intricate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dimension;of great or importance",
    "firstOption": "magnitude",
    "secondOption": "initiate",
    "thirdOption": "astute",
    "fourthOption": "elude",
    "correctOption": "magnitude",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "require;to have to do sth",
    "firstOption": "oblige",
    "secondOption": "abrupt",
    "thirdOption": "convince",
    "fourthOption": "delighted",
    "correctOption": "oblige",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disregard,to ignore or reglect a",
    "firstOption": "mirror",
    "secondOption": "moderate",
    "thirdOption": "erode",
    "fourthOption": "overlook",
    "correctOption": "overlook",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "survey;questionnaire;a vote of public opinion",
    "firstOption": "dim",
    "secondOption": "collide",
    "thirdOption": "pass",
    "fourthOption": "poll",
    "correctOption": "poll",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "pace where something can be found , job , location",
    "firstOption": "practical",
    "secondOption": "predominant",
    "thirdOption": "poll",
    "fourthOption": "position",
    "correctOption": "position",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "functional,convenient or effective",
    "firstOption": "lasting",
    "secondOption": "potential",
    "thirdOption": "practical",
    "fourthOption": "gigantic",
    "correctOption": "practical",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "principal;the most noticeable or powerful element",
    "firstOption": "reaction",
    "secondOption": "predominant",
    "thirdOption": "dominant",
    "fourthOption": "prompt",
    "correctOption": "predominant",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "induce;to cause something to happen;to do quickly;to be on time",
    "firstOption": "prompt",
    "secondOption": "prophetic",
    "thirdOption": "robust",
    "fourthOption": "solid",
    "correctOption": "prompt",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "similar to;alike in some way",
    "firstOption": "analogous",
    "secondOption": "autonomous",
    "thirdOption": "hazardous",
    "fourthOption": "oblivious",
    "correctOption": "analogous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "around;almost correct;not exact",
    "firstOption": "theoretically",
    "secondOption": "prone",
    "thirdOption": "actually",
    "fourthOption": "approximately",
    "correctOption": "approximately",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "oblige,to make something happen by necessity or face",
    "firstOption": "evoke",
    "secondOption": "poll",
    "thirdOption": "clever",
    "fourthOption": "compel",
    "correctOption": "compel",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "overwhelming;difficult;causing worry or fear",
    "firstOption": "feasible",
    "secondOption": "formidable",
    "thirdOption": "face",
    "fourthOption": "ridge",
    "correctOption": "formidable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "annoying;the state of being inside when not desired to be there by others",
    "firstOption": "perceive",
    "secondOption": "intrusive",
    "thirdOption": "incessant",
    "fourthOption": "inactive",
    "correctOption": "intrusive",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "regularly;occuring at specific,determind period of time",
    "firstOption": "energetic",
    "secondOption": "periodic",
    "thirdOption": "chaotic",
    "fourthOption": "tedious",
    "correctOption": "periodic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "inclined to,likely to do something",
    "firstOption": "prone",
    "secondOption": "trap",
    "thirdOption": "prompt",
    "fourthOption": "idol",
    "correctOption": "prone",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "predictive,correctly telling about future events",
    "firstOption": "gigantic",
    "secondOption": "scenic",
    "thirdOption": "prophetic",
    "fourthOption": "prominent",
    "correctOption": "prophetic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "relationship of size or importance when compared to another object or person , dimensions",
    "firstOption": "prophetic",
    "secondOption": "probable",
    "thirdOption": "reliably",
    "fourthOption": "properties",
    "correctOption": "properties",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "freely,willingly;easily",
    "firstOption": "reliable",
    "secondOption": "aptly",
    "thirdOption": "clarify",
    "fourthOption": "readily",
    "correctOption": "readily",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dependably , in a trusted way",
    "firstOption": "reliably",
    "secondOption": "revive",
    "thirdOption": "inevitable",
    "fourthOption": "routinely",
    "correctOption": "reliably",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hesitatingly , unwillingly",
    "firstOption": "routinely",
    "secondOption": "actually",
    "thirdOption": "reluctantly",
    "fourthOption": "crucial",
    "correctOption": "reluctantly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "prominence,fame",
    "firstOption": "renown",
    "secondOption": "abroad",
    "thirdOption": "rigid",
    "fourthOption": "flaw",
    "correctOption": "renown",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to give up something of value for the common good , concession",
    "firstOption": "renown",
    "secondOption": "sacrifice",
    "thirdOption": "flaw",
    "fourthOption": "rigid",
    "correctOption": "sacrifice",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "achievement,a victory",
    "firstOption": "triumph",
    "secondOption": "enrich",
    "thirdOption": "striking",
    "fourthOption": "launch",
    "correctOption": "triumph",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "economical;able to be done;usually refers to something you can do without damage or loss",
    "firstOption": "acceptable",
    "secondOption": "mediorce",
    "thirdOption": "susceptible",
    "fourthOption": "affordable",
    "correctOption": "affordable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "polluted;to make something impure by adding something dirty or a poisonous substance",
    "firstOption": "contaminated",
    "secondOption": "anticipate",
    "thirdOption": "instigate",
    "fourthOption": "initiate",
    "correctOption": "contaminated",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "detectable,noticeable",
    "firstOption": "diverse",
    "secondOption": "feasible",
    "thirdOption": "disperse",
    "fourthOption": "discernible",
    "correctOption": "discernible",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "thriving,active and growing;healthy",
    "firstOption": "flourishing",
    "secondOption": "foster",
    "thirdOption": "launch",
    "fourthOption": "prominent",
    "correctOption": "flourishing",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "preserve;to support;to keep in good condition",
    "firstOption": "myth",
    "secondOption": "archaic",
    "thirdOption": "maintain",
    "fourthOption": "halt",
    "correctOption": "maintain",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "of average quality , not good or bad , average",
    "firstOption": "mediocre",
    "secondOption": "medicine",
    "thirdOption": "flourishing",
    "fourthOption": "parallel",
    "correctOption": "mediocre",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "insignificant , hardly noticeable , scarcest detectable , to ignore , to give little attention",
    "firstOption": "suitable",
    "secondOption": "negligible",
    "thirdOption": "agile",
    "fourthOption": "visibly",
    "correctOption": "negligible",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "to be complementary or appropriate;a good match,compatible",
    "firstOption": "celebrated",
    "secondOption": "enlighten",
    "thirdOption": "elaborate",
    "fourthOption": "well-suited",
    "correctOption": "well-suited",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "strange,unusual;uncommon",
    "firstOption": "reveal",
    "secondOption": "superior",
    "thirdOption": "archaic",
    "fourthOption": "peculiar",
    "correctOption": "peculiar",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "powerful;very strong",
    "firstOption": "myth",
    "secondOption": "avert",
    "thirdOption": "prompt",
    "fourthOption": "potent",
    "correctOption": "potent",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "exceptional , worthy of mention , uncommon",
    "firstOption": "nominal",
    "secondOption": "restore",
    "thirdOption": "remarkable",
    "fourthOption": "revive",
    "correctOption": "remarkable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dispersed;to be spread or separated widely",
    "firstOption": "pattern",
    "secondOption": "scattered",
    "thirdOption": "avert",
    "fourthOption": "documented",
    "correctOption": "scattered",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "steady;having good quality,being well made;firm;not a gas or liquid",
    "firstOption": "mimic",
    "secondOption": "solid",
    "thirdOption": "woo",
    "fourthOption": "steady",
    "correctOption": "solid",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "slight",
    "firstOption": "somewhat",
    "secondOption": "potent",
    "thirdOption": "element",
    "fourthOption": "shed",
    "correctOption": "somewhat",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "monotonous;long and tiring",
    "firstOption": "tedious",
    "secondOption": "mediocre",
    "thirdOption": "swift",
    "fourthOption": "pass",
    "correctOption": "tedious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "concisely;short,usually in time",
    "firstOption": "obviously",
    "secondOption": "shift",
    "thirdOption": "prime",
    "fourthOption": "briefly",
    "correctOption": "briefly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "distribute,to cause to move along a fixed;to move freely",
    "firstOption": "dictate",
    "secondOption": "circulate",
    "thirdOption": "cultivate",
    "fourthOption": "persuade",
    "correctOption": "circulate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "dependably , without changing , keeping the same principles , ideas , or quality",
    "firstOption": "entirely",
    "secondOption": "consistently",
    "thirdOption": "condensed",
    "fourthOption": "potent",
    "correctOption": "consistently",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "display;to show or demonstrate",
    "firstOption": "rigid",
    "secondOption": "enact",
    "thirdOption": "albeit",
    "fourthOption": "exhibit",
    "correctOption": "exhibit",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "establish,to establish;start up",
    "firstOption": "convey",
    "secondOption": "temp",
    "thirdOption": "astute",
    "fourthOption": "found",
    "correctOption": "found",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "inappropriately;not following established rules;not desirable",
    "firstOption": "improperly",
    "secondOption": "impressive",
    "thirdOption": "sharply",
    "fourthOption": "freshly",
    "correctOption": "improperly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "capriciously;acting without thinking",
    "firstOption": "unravel",
    "secondOption": "impulsively",
    "thirdOption": "presumable",
    "fourthOption": "suspect",
    "correctOption": "impulsively",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "carelessly,by accident,without paying attention;unexpectedlyedly",
    "firstOption": "reportedly",
    "secondOption": "intentionally",
    "thirdOption": "inadvertently",
    "fourthOption": "infrequently",
    "correctOption": "infrequently",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "secluded , kept separated from others",
    "firstOption": "isolated",
    "secondOption": "hasten",
    "thirdOption": "broaden",
    "fourthOption": "poll",
    "correctOption": "isolated",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "openly;in a way clearly seen;not done secretly",
    "firstOption": "convert",
    "secondOption": "overtly",
    "thirdOption": "avert",
    "fourthOption": "novel",
    "correctOption": "overtly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "significantly , in a deep way , showing deep knowledge of a subject",
    "firstOption": "prone",
    "secondOption": "promote",
    "thirdOption": "supposedly",
    "fourthOption": "profoundly",
    "correctOption": "profoundly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "quickly , showing sensitivity or quick thinking , showing a quick change in direction",
    "firstOption": "coarse",
    "secondOption": "steady",
    "thirdOption": "handle",
    "fourthOption": "sharply",
    "correctOption": "sharply",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "located;being found in a certain place",
    "firstOption": "accurate",
    "secondOption": "situated",
    "thirdOption": "dictate",
    "fourthOption": "withdraw",
    "correctOption": "situated",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "following , coming after something , afterwards",
    "firstOption": "subsequently",
    "secondOption": "situated",
    "thirdOption": "size",
    "fourthOption": "unmistakable",
    "correctOption": "subsequently",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "clearly able to be determined , indisputable",
    "firstOption": "subsequently",
    "secondOption": "unmistakable",
    "thirdOption": "situated",
    "fourthOption": "dictate",
    "correctOption": "unmistakable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "disorganized;being in compete disorder and confusion",
    "firstOption": "chaotic",
    "secondOption": "halt",
    "thirdOption": "motion",
    "fourthOption": "charisma",
    "correctOption": "chaotic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "typical;no easily recognized quality of something",
    "firstOption": "chaotic",
    "secondOption": "hazardous",
    "thirdOption": "coarse",
    "fourthOption": "characteristic",
    "correctOption": "characteristic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "debatable , something that causes disagreement or argument",
    "firstOption": "controversial",
    "secondOption": "compel",
    "thirdOption": "impartial",
    "fourthOption": "stream",
    "correctOption": "controversial",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "symbolize,to give an example",
    "firstOption": "tightly",
    "secondOption": "actually",
    "thirdOption": "exemplify",
    "fourthOption": "fertile",
    "correctOption": "exemplify",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "satisfying;giving pleasure or a feeling of accomplishment;showing thanks",
    "firstOption": "gain",
    "secondOption": "gratifying",
    "thirdOption": "lasting",
    "fourthOption": "dwelling",
    "correctOption": "gratifying",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "clarify , to understand the meaning of something",
    "firstOption": "moderate",
    "secondOption": "interpret",
    "thirdOption": "encircle",
    "fourthOption": "potent",
    "correctOption": "interpret",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "initiate , to cause something to begin",
    "firstOption": "enrich",
    "secondOption": "dense",
    "thirdOption": "launch",
    "fourthOption": "agile",
    "correctOption": "launch",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "authentic , reasonable , lawful",
    "firstOption": "delicate",
    "secondOption": "inevitable",
    "thirdOption": "legitimate",
    "fourthOption": "fabricate",
    "correctOption": "legitimate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "specific , a certain way or thing , unusual , hard to please",
    "firstOption": "partially",
    "secondOption": "accurate",
    "thirdOption": "particular",
    "fourthOption": "entirely",
    "correctOption": "particular",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "bright;sending out in all direction,especially heat or light",
    "firstOption": "radiant",
    "secondOption": "trait",
    "thirdOption": "evident",
    "fourthOption": "ancient",
    "correctOption": "radiant",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "crest , the top of a mountain range , a raised of any surface",
    "firstOption": "mimic",
    "secondOption": "ridge",
    "thirdOption": "trigger",
    "fourthOption": "vague",
    "correctOption": "ridge",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cover,the length of time or distance from one limit to the other,to cross",
    "firstOption": "span",
    "secondOption": "aptly",
    "thirdOption": "shed",
    "fourthOption": "dim",
    "correctOption": "span",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "instinctive , unplanned , uncontrolled",
    "firstOption": "spacious",
    "secondOption": "precious",
    "thirdOption": "spontaneous",
    "fourthOption": "synthesis",
    "correctOption": "spontaneous",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "river;a natural flow of something; pouring out",
    "firstOption": "alter",
    "secondOption": "stream",
    "thirdOption": "core",
    "fourthOption": "abroad",
    "correctOption": "stream",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "remarkable , drawing special attention to",
    "firstOption": "streamline",
    "secondOption": "erratic",
    "thirdOption": "striking",
    "fourthOption": "trigger",
    "correctOption": "striking",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "appropriately , having a tendency to do something , likely",
    "firstOption": "aptly",
    "secondOption": "halt",
    "thirdOption": "defy",
    "fourthOption": "vital",
    "correctOption": "aptly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "display;a show or exhibit",
    "firstOption": "opposition",
    "secondOption": "preconception",
    "thirdOption": "demonstration",
    "fourthOption": "instigate",
    "correctOption": "demonstration",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "elements,things combined to make something;the contents of something",
    "firstOption": "ingredients",
    "secondOption": "convenient",
    "thirdOption": "inadvertently",
    "fourthOption": "intrusive",
    "correctOption": "ingredients",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "automatically;in an unthinking manner;not chosen",
    "firstOption": "suitable",
    "secondOption": "enrich",
    "thirdOption": "curative",
    "fourthOption": "involuntarily",
    "correctOption": "involuntarily",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "wonder;something that surprises or impresses",
    "firstOption": "parallel",
    "secondOption": "marvel",
    "thirdOption": "assert",
    "fourthOption": "varied",
    "correctOption": "marvel",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "assessable;able to determine how much or how many",
    "firstOption": "remarkable",
    "secondOption": "presumable",
    "thirdOption": "measurable",
    "fourthOption": "formidable",
    "correctOption": "measurable",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "medium,not too much, not too little",
    "firstOption": "moderate",
    "secondOption": "mirror",
    "thirdOption": "assert",
    "fourthOption": "accelerate",
    "correctOption": "moderate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "strange,unusual",
    "firstOption": "odd",
    "secondOption": "poll",
    "thirdOption": "emit",
    "fourthOption": "bear",
    "correctOption": "odd",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "image;a picture or element cast back",
    "firstOption": "reliable",
    "secondOption": "reflection",
    "thirdOption": "caution",
    "fourthOption": "revive",
    "correctOption": "reflection",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "presumable;according to reports or hearsay;widely believed or accepted",
    "firstOption": "poll",
    "secondOption": "routinely",
    "thirdOption": "supposedly",
    "fourthOption": "justify",
    "correctOption": "supposedly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "consistent;continuing in a constant way;remaining strong",
    "firstOption": "obtain",
    "secondOption": "sheltered",
    "thirdOption": "sustained",
    "fourthOption": "hasten",
    "correctOption": "sustained",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "marks,a sign or object that represents something or somebody marks",
    "firstOption": "durable",
    "secondOption": "limber",
    "thirdOption": "poll",
    "fourthOption": "symbols",
    "correctOption": "symbols",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "combination;to mixing of separate things to form a whole",
    "firstOption": "pass",
    "secondOption": "synthesis",
    "thirdOption": "suspect",
    "fourthOption": "striking",
    "correctOption": "synthesis",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "concrete;real;that which can be felt",
    "firstOption": "negligible",
    "secondOption": "tangible",
    "thirdOption": "durable",
    "fourthOption": "caliber",
    "correctOption": "tangible",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "firmly , being fixed in place , close , leabing no freedom",
    "firstOption": "tightly",
    "secondOption": "archaic",
    "thirdOption": "wanton",
    "fourthOption": "situated",
    "correctOption": "tightly",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "irritating , making worse , annoying",
    "firstOption": "agitate",
    "secondOption": "annoying",
    "thirdOption": "curative",
    "fourthOption": "aggravating",
    "correctOption": "aggravating",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "diversion , something that holds interest and is enjoyable",
    "firstOption": "amusement",
    "secondOption": "avert",
    "thirdOption": "assert",
    "fourthOption": "reject",
    "correctOption": "amusement",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "possibly , feasibly , believably",
    "firstOption": "encircle",
    "secondOption": "convey",
    "thirdOption": "condensed",
    "fourthOption": "conceivably",
    "correctOption": "conceivably",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "alter;to change from one from or state to another",
    "firstOption": "convert",
    "secondOption": "convenient",
    "thirdOption": "convey",
    "fourthOption": "coherent",
    "correctOption": "convert",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "healing , being able to restore to good condition",
    "firstOption": "curative",
    "secondOption": "curious",
    "thirdOption": "disruptive",
    "fourthOption": "selective",
    "correctOption": "curative",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "weakening",
    "firstOption": "persistent",
    "secondOption": "deplete",
    "thirdOption": "resilient",
    "fourthOption": "debilitating",
    "correctOption": "debilitating",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "consume,to use up;to reduce greatly",
    "firstOption": "dense",
    "secondOption": "elude",
    "thirdOption": "agile",
    "fourthOption": "deplete",
    "correctOption": "deplete",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "limited,of a certain amount;having an end;not infinite",
    "firstOption": "oblige",
    "secondOption": "revive",
    "thirdOption": "finite",
    "fourthOption": "handle",
    "correctOption": "finite",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "observe;to sense;to become aware of",
    "firstOption": "overcome",
    "secondOption": "perceive",
    "thirdOption": "prime",
    "fourthOption": "benefit",
    "correctOption": "perceive",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "safety , the feeling of freedom",
    "firstOption": "perceive",
    "secondOption": "elude",
    "thirdOption": "security",
    "fourthOption": "severe",
    "correctOption": "security",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "poisonous;harmful;capable of being fatal",
    "firstOption": "toxic",
    "secondOption": "defy",
    "thirdOption": "erratic",
    "fourthOption": "advice",
    "correctOption": "toxic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "peacefulness,calm,quietness",
    "firstOption": "amenity",
    "secondOption": "requisite",
    "thirdOption": "tranquility",
    "fourthOption": "tangible",
    "correctOption": "tranquility",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "retain,to catch and hold onto,usually by trickery;deceived",
    "firstOption": "defy",
    "secondOption": "flaw",
    "thirdOption": "triumph",
    "fourthOption": "trap",
    "correctOption": "trap",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "clearly true , absolutely",
    "firstOption": "undeniably",
    "secondOption": "underestimated",
    "thirdOption": "triumph",
    "fourthOption": "amenity",
    "correctOption": "undeniably",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "miscalculated;guessed lower than the actual quality or quantity",
    "firstOption": "celebrated",
    "secondOption": "underestimated",
    "thirdOption": "fundamental",
    "fourthOption": "widespread",
    "correctOption": "underestimated",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "recognize,to know.remember,and accept the existence of something",
    "firstOption": "solid",
    "secondOption": "release",
    "thirdOption": "acknowledge",
    "fourthOption": "accelerate",
    "correctOption": "acknowledge",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "obtain,to gain or come to possess",
    "firstOption": "volume",
    "secondOption": "astute",
    "thirdOption": "acclaim",
    "fourthOption": "acquire",
    "correctOption": "acquire",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "incorporate,to be come a part of",
    "firstOption": "assimilate",
    "secondOption": "analyze",
    "thirdOption": "dictate",
    "fourthOption": "initiate",
    "correctOption": "assimilate",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "selection;a variety",
    "firstOption": "omit",
    "secondOption": "assortment",
    "thirdOption": "scarcely",
    "fourthOption": "assert",
    "correctOption": "assortment",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "quality,the standard of,the degree of goodness",
    "firstOption": "varied",
    "secondOption": "clever",
    "thirdOption": "caliber",
    "fourthOption": "valid",
    "correctOption": "caliber",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "summarized , made smaller , shortened , merged",
    "firstOption": "condensed",
    "secondOption": "engender",
    "thirdOption": "convince",
    "fourthOption": "concur",
    "correctOption": "condensed",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "inconsistent;not agreeing with the fact or previous statements made on the subject;declare wrong",
    "firstOption": "predictable",
    "secondOption": "conform",
    "thirdOption": "contradictory",
    "fourthOption": "sporadic",
    "correctOption": "contradictory",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ignore,to pay no attention",
    "firstOption": "distribute",
    "secondOption": "shed",
    "thirdOption": "dictate",
    "fourthOption": "disregard",
    "correctOption": "disregard",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "cherished;having much monetary or sentimental value;beautiful",
    "firstOption": "periodic",
    "secondOption": "propose",
    "thirdOption": "precarious",
    "fourthOption": "precious",
    "correctOption": "precious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "renowned,famous;having a high position",
    "firstOption": "prosperous",
    "secondOption": "motion",
    "thirdOption": "prominent",
    "fourthOption": "coarse",
    "correctOption": "prominent",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "demanded;needed for a special purpose",
    "firstOption": "revive",
    "secondOption": "extensive",
    "thirdOption": "requisite",
    "fourthOption": "reliable",
    "correctOption": "requisite",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "separate;to organize;to make clear",
    "firstOption": "prone",
    "secondOption": "unravel",
    "thirdOption": "compel",
    "fourthOption": "erratic",
    "correctOption": "unravel",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "unclear , ambiguous",
    "firstOption": "elude",
    "secondOption": "volume",
    "thirdOption": "coarse",
    "fourthOption": "vague",
    "correctOption": "vague",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "huge;very much;very large",
    "firstOption": "lack",
    "secondOption": "omit",
    "thirdOption": "vast",
    "fourthOption": "trait",
    "correctOption": "vast",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "quantity , the amount of something contained in a space",
    "firstOption": "endure",
    "secondOption": "volume",
    "thirdOption": "hue",
    "fourthOption": "oblige",
    "correctOption": "volume",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "appeal,a special quality that endears other people to the person who has this quality",
    "firstOption": "curative",
    "secondOption": "charisma",
    "thirdOption": "clarify",
    "fourthOption": "handle",
    "correctOption": "charisma",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "astute ,  intelligent , resourceful",
    "firstOption": "marvel",
    "secondOption": "clever",
    "thirdOption": "deplete",
    "fourthOption": "element",
    "correctOption": "clever",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "persuade , to make someone see things your way",
    "firstOption": "endure",
    "secondOption": "currency",
    "thirdOption": "convince",
    "fourthOption": "blind",
    "correctOption": "convince",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "persevere;to last;to suffer pain",
    "firstOption": "enhance",
    "secondOption": "endure",
    "thirdOption": "emerge",
    "fourthOption": "dense",
    "correctOption": "endure",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "relinquish,to give up;to have something taken away;usually by rule or regulation",
    "firstOption": "coherent",
    "secondOption": "creep",
    "thirdOption": "forfeit",
    "fourthOption": "perceive",
    "correctOption": "forfeit",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "hazardous;not safe,firm,or steady",
    "firstOption": "readily",
    "secondOption": "spacious",
    "thirdOption": "charisma",
    "fourthOption": "precarious",
    "correctOption": "precarious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "intense , extreme, harmful",
    "firstOption": "severe",
    "secondOption": "adverse",
    "thirdOption": "avert",
    "fourthOption": "convert",
    "correctOption": "severe",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "erratic;not consistent,irregular",
    "firstOption": "sporadic",
    "secondOption": "pass",
    "thirdOption": "periodic",
    "fourthOption": "archaic",
    "correctOption": "sporadic",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ignorant,to be unaware of or forgetful",
    "firstOption": "hazardous",
    "secondOption": "unique",
    "thirdOption": "fallacious",
    "fourthOption": "oblivious",
    "correctOption": "oblivious",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "senseless , done without thought or consideration",
    "firstOption": "weak",
    "secondOption": "wanton",
    "thirdOption": "handle",
    "fourthOption": "restore",
    "correctOption": "wanton",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "ineffective , not strong , incapable",
    "firstOption": "core",
    "secondOption": "span",
    "thirdOption": "pass",
    "fourthOption": "weak",
    "correctOption": "weak",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "extensive;found everwhere",
    "firstOption": "element",
    "secondOption": "isolated",
    "thirdOption": "widespread",
    "fourthOption": "somewhere",
    "correctOption": "widespread",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "insight;knowledge and understanding",
    "firstOption": "withdraw",
    "secondOption": "arid",
    "thirdOption": "wisdom",
    "fourthOption": "shed",
    "correctOption": "wisdom",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "humor , joke , witticism",
    "firstOption": "lasting",
    "secondOption": "mimic",
    "thirdOption": "witticism",
    "fourthOption": "intricate",
    "correctOption": "witticism",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "attract,to make efforts to attain or gain something",
    "firstOption": "woo",
    "secondOption": "idol",
    "thirdOption": "myth",
    "fourthOption": "defy",
    "correctOption": "woo",
    "category": "450_english_to_english"
  }
]
